<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on idx01 Catalog</title><link>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on idx01 Catalog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://idx01.whistler.page/build/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Average Tuesday</title><link>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/average-tuesday/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/average-tuesday/</guid><description>Commission for: Noah Layta See the blog post here. Average Tuesday &amp;hellip;I should probably get up soon. I&amp;rsquo;ve been asleep long enough. Three hundred years or so of rest? &amp;hellip;Sure.~ That&amp;rsquo;s enough.
Taking a moment, I squirmed to get up, stretching in the process. Nonexistent bones crack, even in my tails. I&amp;rsquo;m getting old&amp;hellip; No, I&amp;rsquo;m already old. But what to do, now that I&amp;rsquo;m awake? I do not exactly feel like going back to sleep&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Debug Mode</title><link>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/debug-mode/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 01:34:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/debug-mode/</guid><description>Commission for: Anonymous See the blog post here. Debug Mode Look, before I get into this, I just wanted to see what the fuss was about. That&amp;rsquo;s it, that&amp;rsquo;s all I wanted. I played OMORI. Start to finish, front to back. Hell, I&amp;rsquo;m even starting to get tired of seeing that kid stare at me on the title screen, so I stopped playing the game for a while. That was, until one of my friends sent me a mod.</description></item><item><title>Self Cauterization</title><link>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/self-cauterization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 01:11:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/self-cauterization/</guid><description>NOTES:
Something I wrote myself. See the blog post here. Self Cauterization None of us knew how it happened. None of us knew where they got all of the firepower that they had. Yet place by place, we were pushed back. Back further than our original homes, and all we knew was becoming further and further away every day. We couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep the lights on, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have the Great Zapfish anymore.</description></item><item><title>Frozen Welcomes</title><link>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/frozen-welcomes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 22:11:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://idx01.whistler.page/build/frozen-welcomes/</guid><description>NOTES:
Something I wrote myself. See the blog post here. Frozen Welcomes I didn’t even know what time it was. All I know was that it was far later at night than I was used to. Through the only window in the broken down room, the first flecks of snow started to fall. Finally, winter truly started&amp;hellip; though it’s not as if I could enjoy any of it, I was grounded.</description></item></channel></rss>